So the financial year
20-20 cricket
financial results of ICICI Lombard are in front of you all, all the
certificates given on India are
in legs, so first of all
we check the income of this company, so if
compared with the December 2020 quarter and December 2021 quarter, then in September it had
generated an income of approximately 4499.03 crores and
in the December 2021 quarter, the
income was 3854.14, so even now if we
talk about the income growth of this company, then on a daily
basis the company has a very good
positive income, but unfortunately if we
discuss about the income expenses, then in
December the
company had
spent 485.58 crores to close and
in the December 2021 quarter,
this company had spent 350081.07 crores, so
now this is the net profit of the company, that is, if we
talk about the profit after tax till now, then in
December  In the quarter of 2020, the
company has
posted a profit of 52.53 crores.
In the quarter of September 2022, the company had
posted a profit of 590.53 crores
and in December
2021, the company had
posted a profit of 7.53 crores. So, if we
talk about the profit growth of this company, then the
profit of the company has come out
in positive like the income of the company, but unfortunately the
company has gone
and as far as the value of the company's earnings, that is, earnings
per equity share, is concerned, then the
value of December has come out to be
12.03 and that of December has come out to be
6.47. So, the
growth of the company's earnings is also coming out in negative on quarter-on-quarter basis and positive on year-on-year basis like the profit and income of the company,
as
you can see the stuff here, so now
if we look at the overall, then in the quarter of December 2020, the
company has shown 50% growth
in positive.  50% were
seen in negative, the growth on inter quarter on quarter
basis is negative and on anti
idea don air basis it is in positive,
so the official result of December 2020
quarter has
performed well in December.